{
    "subject": "resource/Irfan_Mensur",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Sarajevo",
    "human_readable": "Irfan Mensur was born in Sarajevo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8618491888046265,
            "question": "Where was Irfan Mensur born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8335099220275879,
            "question": "In what country was Irfan Mensur born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7075555920600891,
            "question": "Were there any famous people born in Sarajevo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6283052563667297,
            "question": "Is there any notable information about Irfan Mensur's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5244554281234741,
            "question": "What is Irfan Mensur known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3564395308494568,
            "question": "What is Sarajevo known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3427770137786865,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Irfan Mensur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2930241823196411,
            "question": "What is the culture like in Sarajevo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2815362811088562,
            "question": "Is there a significant historical event associated with Sarajevo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02858537994325161,
            "question": "What other cities in Bosnia and Herzegovina are notable?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Irfan Mensur was born in Sarajevo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8569_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a significant historical event associated with Sarajevo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8569_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the culture like in Sarajevo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8569_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Irfan Mensur?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8569_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8569_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8569_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8569_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8569_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8569_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8569_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8569_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8569_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8569_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8569_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents mention that Irfan Mensur was born on January 19, 1952, in Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina, Yugoslavia. This supports the triple \"Irfan Mensur was born in Sarajevo\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Irfan Mensur was born in Sarajevo, which directly supports the statement \"Irfan Mensur was born in Sarajevo.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}